Sunday David

Software Engineer | Full Stack Developer

Location: Uyo, Nigeria

Phone: +2349079029135

Email: sundaydavidudoekong@gmail.com

LinkedIn profile: https://www.linkedin.com/in/sunday-david-951369266

GitHub profile: https://github.com/sundayjava

ABOUT

Dedicated, enthusiastic and competent full-stack developer with 3+ years of experience in application layers, presentation layers, and databases. Dedicated professional with proven performance in management, leadership and communication. Detailed in problem-solving and planning. Proficient in both Frontend and Backend technologies. Seeking to further improve my Web/Mobile Development and Devops skills and looking forward to getting an opportunity as a full-stack developer to make an immediate contribution to your organization.

SKILLS

Frontend Skills

- Javascript
- Typescript
- React.js e.t.c

Backend Skills

Java

• Springboot e.t.c

Extra Skills

- Hibernete
- JWT/OAuth
- AWS/Microservices
- Git/Version control
- Postgres/Mysql
- Bootstrap/Tailwind/Material Ui/ yup etc.

EXPERIENCE

Jiggle, Uyo, Nigeria - Fullstack(Remote)

Jul 2023 - Dec 2023

• Jiggle: Development of a budgeting and payments application that allows users to deposit funds and make budgets with their funds and also allows users to make payments for items, goods or products bought in places where the application is registered for payments.

Ebsirs, Ebonyi, Nigeria - Frontend(Contract/Remote)

Dec 2022 - May 2023

• Ebsirs: Development of an internal revenue system for ebonyi state government that allows users to pay tax and also track their task with the code that will be automatically generated.

Start Innovation Hub, Uyo, Nigeria - Fullstack Onsite(Full-time)
Sep 2021 - Ended

• Hamlet: Hamlet is a Multi Tenant Human Resource Management platform created for easy employee management. It is used to manage payment, Employees and also recruiting without using external tools.

PROJECT

- Blog platform
- Library management with stripe payment
- Simple e-commerce platform

EDUCATION

Akanu Ibiam Federal Polytechnic Unwana, Ebonyi State - National Diploma 2019 - 2021

Computer Science Student, graduated with Upper

Federal Polytechnic Oko, Anambra - Higher National Diploma 2021 - 2023

Computer Science Student, graduated with Distinction.

HOBBIES

- Research
- Gaming
- Reading Books

Links to All site are Available but not all will be displayed due to the NON-DISCLOSURE AGREEMENT sign in this company